[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Diego] I've been wanting
to give you this.
I love you so much.
[Natalie] I didn't save
your life for nothing.
I was hoping you would like me back.
[Jepoy] It meant nothing, right?
I don't want to see you together.
-Why not?
-Isn't it obvious?!
Jepoy, I like you.
-I'm sorry.
-Anna, wait! Anna!
I will come back, and when I do,
I'll come back with a vengeance!
[Anna] You look a little
happier than usual.
[Arnaldo] I think I saw an angel.
Is she my brother's girlfriend?
[Anna] I know they're getting there.
She's our friend, Lily.
If she's your friend,
can you introduce me to her?
[Jepoy] This is dangerous.
Arnaldo was crazy obsessed
with Ivy back then.
What if his memories come back?
[Lily] You're the one who texted me?
[Emilia] And you're the one
investigating my mother,
trying to connect her to Red Dragon.
This is a clone of Mercedes' phone.
[Jepoy] You can keep
track of all her calls
and text messages from here.
[Camia] It's confirmed.
That's another piece of evidence
that will prove
that Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
[Lily] The people of Poblacion
Ardiente will soon know
that their supposed angel
is actually a devil in disguise.
[doctor] Sometimes, you just need
to jump-start the patient's brain.
By that, I mean images that'll
ignite an intense emotion.
[Julio] I'll get you back, Arnaldo.
You'll be the man you once were.
I promise you that.
[Jepoy] I'll get that.
I'll be right with you.
Excuse us for a while. We'll just talk.
Um, Arnaldo…
I'm sorry I haven't
visited you in a while.
I haven't been feeling very well recently.
You've been sick?
Are you all right now? Do you feel better?
Yes, thank you. I'm slowly recovering.
In fact…
the doctors are surprised
at my speedy recovery.
But what they don't know…
is that I have a new secret weapon.
This is my new secret weapon.
The inspired word of God,
the Bible.
You know what?
It's because of you…
that I started reading this again.
[chuckles]
-Praise the Lord.
-[Julio laughs]
Thank you, grandson.
You know, you inspired me.
This brought light into my life.
Seems like karma has hit
the Ardientes hard.
Look at Julio.
[Jepoy] Looks like he's gone nuts.
Maybe because his family is all broken up.
Anna, don't forget.
That man in front of you?
That's Julio Ardiente.
Even Satan fears him.
Everyone can change.
Look at Arnaldo.
Even you.
Me?
I'm glad you didn't hurt Arnaldo earlier.
Only because you don't want me to.
[Helena on voice recording]
I've already settled
my problem with Mr. Yi
regarding the gun shipment.
[Mercedes] I have one
other concern, Madam.
Emilia says she wants
to get rid of someone.
[Helena] Prioritize the shipment.
And I will take care of my daughter.
See, Attorney? Heard all that?
It's clear. That was
Helena Montoya's voice.
This proves that she is Red Dragon.
We can definitely use this as evidence,
but we still need a whistleblower
to prove that Helena
Montoya is Red Dragon.
Well, I have good news, Attorney.
Just wait.
I've got an ace up my sleeve.
Well, I won't stay long.
So, this is farewell for now.
Are you sure…
you don't want to come
back with me to the mansion?
I really don't, Grandpa.
My mission is here.
But it was nice to see you again.
Okay. I understand.
Stay safe.
Um, thank you. I'll be on my way.
Uh… Grandpa, your Bible.
You forgot it.
[Julio chuckles]
Did you know that…
this Bible was from your grandmother?
Right now, I'm thinking…
it's better if I leave this to you.
Think of it as a memento from her.
[Arnaldo] Uh…
-Okay.
-I'm sure she'd be happy.
-All right, Grandpa.
-Take care, Arnaldo.
-I'll go ahead.
-Okay.
[sinister music playing]
Yes, Madam?
Call Mr. Yi.
Tell him to expect the
shipment tomorrow evening.
Yes.
[tense music]
[keys beep]
Crap!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Madam.
My phone just keeps blacking out.
Since when?
This morning.
Give me your phone.
[sighs] You know, when
your phone blacks out,
it means it's been cloned.
That's impossible, Madam.
Because I always have it with me.
Shut up!
Your phone has been cloned!
[phone clatters]
Get Romulo!
[ominous music playing]
"Then you will know the truth
and the truth will set you free."
[ominous music continues playing]
I'll go to Myla at the safe house
and ask her if she knows
the name Helena Montoya.
Maybe she can help us find
even more evidence.
-Don't leave my daughter.
-Yes, ma'am.
Take care, dear.
Get the car ready.
Lily's pushing through
with the investigation?
That's how she is.
A little rain won't stop her.
Camia, she's got a big storm coming.
And my daughter is ready for that.
Have you seen her bodyguards?
A light breeze could blow them over.
They're not ready for
Red Dragon's typhoon.
My daughter doesn't need them, Damian.
She's a fighter on her own.
Those bodyguards are only
there to make me feel better.
I trust that my daughter
is ready for what she's facing.
I wish you would too.
Especially if you want to be
a part of our family.
[Romulo] Madam…
this is the dark web's latest technology.
We traced the IMEI number of
whoever tapped Mercedes' phone.
And?
She was right.
The one behind all this…
is Lily Cruz.
[breathes heavily]
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
What? How did that happen?
All right. I'll deal with it.
Lily needs to know about this.
[Emilia] Hi, Mama!
I bought you some scarves.
I did some shopping today.
Hello!
I can see you're busy. I should leave now.
-Sorry.
-No.
Just stay here, Emilia. Sit beside me.
Oh, okay.
What happened?
I just realized
that I'm allergic to flowers.
Lilies, in particular.
[tense music continues playing]
Lily, where's the cellphone I gave you?
It's here. Have a seat.
Why?
My source said they traced the phone.
So you need to give it to me.
If that's true, then that means…
Red Dragon already knows
that we cloned their phone.
Probably. That's why I need
to dispose of it.
No need, Jepoy.
I'm sure Red Dragon already knows
that I'm her enemy.
[ominous music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[Diego] Arnaldo?
Arnaldo!
Arnaldo.
Are you okay?
I think I'm committing a sin against God.
What do you mean?
Well…
I've been having some thoughts lately.
About a woman.
I don't know if it's all just a dream, or…
if it's a fragment of my memories.
Well, what do you see?
[sighs] Bad things.
I feel things…
Lustful things toward her.
[tense music playing]
For the life of me, I don't know…
why I see her that way.
And, I know she's
a friend of yours, Diego.
So, I hope you can forgive me
for thinking such things about her.
I hope you don't hate me for it.
I don't hate you.
But, I think I should keep this for now.
Yeah. Maybe that'll make
the bad dreams go away.
Where did you get this, by the way?
I found it inside the Bible
Grandpa gave me.
[suspenseful music]
[Helena] I can't allow my true identity
to be exposed to the public.
My empire…
the empire that I've worked so hard for
is going to crumble the moment
people find out who I really am.
And that's the problem, Mama.
Good old Lily Cruz.
She's like a mosquito.
She'll keep coming back
no matter what you do,
just to suck your precious blood dry.
[tense music]
There's only one way to kill
those pesky mosquitoes.
By crushing them!
Love it, Mama! [giggles]
[phone ringing]
-[phone ringing]
-[Helena scoffs]
Speaking of the mosquito.
-I think she actually heard us.
-[phone ringing]
[phone ringing]
Beautiful morning, Lily!
Not as beautiful as you are, Mama.
To what do I owe the
pleasure of this call?
Um…
Well, I missed you, so I was thinking…
-lunch?
-[Helena laughs]
My, what a coincidence!
I was just thinking
of the exact same thing.
Oh, really, Mama?
So… See you.
Julio!
[Julio] Psst! Don't.
It's okay. Leave us for a while.
We'll just talk.
He won't hurt me. He's a good boy.
Diego…
I'm afraid today is just not your day.
I don't have any spare
change left to give you.
[tuts] Sorry.
What's all this about?
Do you even care for Arnaldo?
More than my life.
If that's true, don't ruin his new life.
Don't deprive him of his happiness!
Ooh… Happiness, you say?
Whose happiness?
Yours?
Or…
Lily Cruz's?
Diego…
[scoffs]
I know Arnaldo well.
He won't be too happy when he finds out
what you've been doing to him.
So, don't go lecturing me…
about Arnaldo's happiness.
Don't you dare come near my brother again.
Why are you furious?
Is it because…
Arnaldo is slowly starting to remember…
Ivy Aguas?
Ivy Aguas is dead.
Both she…
and the old Arnaldo!
Stay away from my brother!
[laughs]
The ghosts are haunting you, Diego.
[laughs viciously]
They're running after you.
Hmm.
That bastard…
has been crossing me for far too long!
[Julio] You idiot!
Go ahead, Grandpa.
I'm not the same kid you used
to abuse. You can't scare me.
[Julio] Who do you think you are?
I raised you!
I fed you and sent you to school.
I'm ashamed to even call you an Ardiente.
[Diego] Julio, your time is up.
Because I'll make sure that
from this day on,
evil will no longer reign in Ardiente.
Julio Ardiente…
-is a cheater!
-Mr. Torillo, why are you here?
[Diego] We are here to protest against
Julio Ardiente's proclamation
as governor of this province!
Julio Ardiente!
I believe this is your money.
The money you used
to bribe Secretary Martel!
And who do we have here?!
You just can't accept defeat, can you?
You only won…
-Sir!
-…because you cheated!
As long as I'm alive,
you'll never be the
governor of this province.
Remember that!
Do you even care for Arnaldo?
Don't ruin his new life.
Stay away from my brother!
Colonel.
I want you to kill Diego Torillo now!
Jepoy?
What are you doing?
Where's Lily?
She's still at Mister Pandoy's
birthday party.
-Aren't you going?
-I forgot!
I'll just catch up. I should go now.
Jepoy, wait.
Thanks for helping Lily expose Red Dragon.
That's my role, Anna.
To protect you and Lily.
And be a true friend.
Thanks.
I hope…
that doesn't change.
[soft music playing]
Everything changes, Anna.
Doesn't it?
[soft music continues playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Okay, I'm on my way. Bye.
Jepoy, I have to go.
[sighs]
[exhales]
It should be simple, right?
All I want
is for Diego Torillo to die!
Yes, sir.
Once you've done it,
bring me his corpse
as proof
that you did it successfully.
Yes, sir.
Colonel.
This is how it's going to go down.
Diego Torillo takes his last breath
by sunset.
Or you just might not see
another sunrise in your life.
Am I clear?
-Yes, sir.
-Go.
-My, Loring, that's a lot!
-Of course.
-We're expecting visitors.
-[Lily] Miss Loring!
-See? They're here.
-It's Lily!
Lily!
-Mr. Pandoy!
-Nanny! Uncle!
Lily! Diego, son.
-Happy, happy birthday!
-Oh, my! Thank you.
-There we go.
-I'm so happy you visited us.
Of course, Mr. Pandoy.
-I wouldn't miss your birthday.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
I heard you cooked
a lot yesterday, Miss Loring.
I'm sorry I couldn't come.
-It's okay. Diego ate it all.
-[Loring laughs]
He still has grease on his lips. [laughs]
[Loring] Yeah. He licked everything clean.
I almost put the dishes away
without washing them.
Hang on, I'm innocent over here.
And it's Uncle's birthday.
Shine the spotlight on him.
-Me?
-That's right!
-Well, since it's…
-Oh, my.
-Mr. Pandoy's birthday…
-What's all that?
Hold on. Wait.
[Pandoy] That's a lot!
-Are they all for me?
-Yes. And these too.
-Wow!
-This one's from my mom…
-This is a lot!
-These are from Anna and Jepoy.
-I'm very grateful. Thank you.
-Wow!
-Oh!
-Oh.
Diego, Jepoy… [chuckles]
These are so nice.
-There's more, Nanny.
-Oh, this is such a cute box!
-Look at this!
-I bet that's expensive.
-You think so?
-It's probably a ring…
-Let's see.
-…a necklace, or a bracelet.
[Loring] Surprise!
Ooh. Who's this from?
[Diego] It's…
from Arnaldo.
[tense music playing]
That demon.
I'm sorry…
but we won't accept gifts
from a known murderer.
Give it back.
Come on, Nanny.
Nanny, Uncle, my brother has changed.
Maybe we could give him a chance.
Why? Have you already forgotten?
He's the reason why your
Uncle Pandoy almost died!
[Pandoy scoffs]
I haven't forgotten that.
Then, I hope you understand
why we can't do what you're asking for.
I'm aware that your brother's still sick.
But just because he's forgotten
all the crimes he did to us…
doesn't mean we can just forget
all the pain and suffering
he put us through.
He didn't just scratch the surface,
he went and cut us all deep.
I just want all of us to get along.
-Excuse me.
-Diego--
[Pandoy sighs heavily]
[sighs heavily] Sorry, Lily.
Uh…
No worries, Mr. Pandoy.
I understand how you feel.
[Pandoy sighs heavily]
I'll talk to him.
[Pandoy exhales]
Diego!
Diego, wait.
Come on, let's go back.
I'll just stay here awhile.
Diego, just try to understand
Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy.
I do understand them.
It's just that I want
all of us to get along.
That's the best thing for everyone.
I understand that.
And yes, Arnaldo is your brother.
But it's not that easy to forget
the pain your brother caused.
[Anna] Okay, kids. That's it…
-for today's storytelling.
-[guitar riffs]
[Anna] Let's continue tomorrow, okay?
[girl] One more story, Teacher Anna.
-Please.
-You go ahead.
You go on ahead.
No, you go back there because
it's Mr. Pandoy's birthday.
I'll be right with you.
[Diego] Really.
Go on ahead.
[sad music playing]
[Anna] Why don't you kids
listen to Arnaldo for now, okay?
[boy] Yes, ma'am. Come on!
[guitar riffs]
[Arnaldo] Oh! [giggles]
Wanna hear a song?
[Arnaldo] Let's see…
Go on.
Hold on…
-Can we go play by the river?
-Just a sec, um…
-Please, Arnaldo?
-Please!
[girl] Over there!
Um, all right. All right.
[girl] Let's go!
Sure, let's go!
[girl] Let's go.
You wanna talk about what's bothering you?
It's not like I've forgotten
about all the things Arnaldo did.
But he's changed.
You've seen it too, right?
He's a new man!
But you still can't force
everyone else to forgive him.
To them, he's still the same old Arnaldo.
The one who hurt them,
the one who abused them.
The one who killed Nanny Carlotta.
So, you too, huh?
You can't forgive him either?
At first, it was really hard
for me to forgive Arnaldo.
He killed the kindest person
I'd ever met in my entire life.
And I just couldn't forget that
whenever I saw him.
But you and Lily helped me
let that grudge go.
And, the more I see him now,
the less I remember
all the bad things he's done.
It's like this Arnaldo is someone else.
So, do the same thing
for Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy.
Help them forget all those
horrible things about Arnaldo.
Don't worry.
Jepoy and I are here for you.
You know that, right?
[soft music playing]
Eat up.
[sentimental music playing]
[Pandoy exhales]
Uh…
Come here, Diego.
We're sorry about what happened earlier.
Now, come on. Join us.
Sit.
Eat with us.
[Diego] No, it's not that.
I should be the one apologizing.
Uncle, Nanny, I'm sorry.
I let my emotions get the better of me.
I wasn't thinking…
about all the horrible
things Arnaldo did to you.
But, I'm going to prove to you…
that my brother really has changed.
So, I'm begging you, please…
give him another chance.
He needs our help and our support.
-[Pandoy sighs]
-We'll try, Diego. For you.
Oh, my. [sighs heavily]
Now, hold on.
It's a birthday party, right?
Enough with the drama.
-[Pandoy laughs]
-We should be happy.
Well, I know I wasn't being dramatic.
-It's a party!
-Food makes everything better.
-All I need is this.
-But, of course!
Fritters!
There's more where that came from.
-Don't forget the ice cream!
-It's great.
[Loring and Pandoy giggle]
-But wait--
-Pile it up high.
-You can have it all!
-It's not the ice cream.
I think something's missing.
-What?
-Hold on, give me a minute…
-What is it?
-We're not missing anything.
Be right back. Don't move, okay?
I'll just go get something.
-Where are you going?
-Wait.
Hey!
-Where's he going?
-Don't move, okay?
I'll just go get something.
-But, your food--
-Wait here.
[laughing] Where's he going?
[laughing]
What do we do?
-Anyway…
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you.
-Once more.
[in sweet voice] Happy birthday to you.
[in silly voice] Whoops, maybe tomorrow.
[Pandoy laughing] Hey!
It won't be my birthday by then.
Okay, fine. Here.
-No, thanks.
-Oh, stop sulking!
You're going on a
lunch date with Lily Cruz?
I wanna watch!
I wanna watch how you crush that woman.
I'm sorry, Emilia.
-But… no.
-But, Mama, I wanna go.
I wanna check whether or not
she really is indestructible.
I want you to stay and watch.
But, Mama…
I can take her out on my own.
Let me handle her.
[Emilia sighs] Mama…
Emilia…
for once…
you need to stay behind.
You get too emotional
when Lily Cruz is around.
You need a solid presence of mind.
You have to be 10 steps
ahead of your enemy.
And emotions will only get in the way.
So, you have to stay and watch.
Okay, Mama.
I will watch how the queen works.
Exactly.
[explosions]
[Lily] You're the one who
blew up the media complex!
[Myla] That's right!
Where's Madam Red Dragon?
You just missed her.
Do you know what this is?
[Lily] Ouch!
It could be painful.
It could be deadly.
[tense music playing]
I'm done playing pretend, Helena Montoya.
So now,
I'm going to make sure
you admit it yourself.
You are none other than Red Dragon.
-Where's Diego?
-He left.
Those are some big catfish.
Well, I caught them.
Unlike Diego's.
[sweet music playing]
So, why did he drop by?
He had a fight with
Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy.
That's their problem. What's with the hug?
I gave him advice, and he felt better,
so he hugged me.
You seem happy about it.
So what if I'm happy?
Are you jealous?
Yes, I am. Is that a problem?
I'm jealous because I don't just like you,
I really like you too, Anna.
I don't know what to do.
You're always in my head and in my heart.
Jepoy, I'm not the one in your heart.
It's always been Lily,
ever since we were kids.
I just pretended to
be Lily, but I'm not her.
In case you forgot, Jepoy,
you almost gave your life for her.
I haven't forgotten, Anna.
I know you're not Lily.
But it's all clear to me now, Anna.
The only reason I did
what they told me was
because of my debt of gratitude
towards her and Miss Prianka.
But now…
I--
I don't know what's happening.
I don't owe you anything, but…
I don't know why I'm
feeling these things for you.
[Jepoy scoffs] You know what? I give up.
Because of what happened,
I told Natalie to stay away.
If only I'd known that…
If only I'd known what?
That I had no place in your heart.
[upbeat music playing]
Thanks to Diego.
What does he have that I don't?
Jepoy, Diego is important to me
because he's my friend.
And that's that. It won't change.
It won't change, huh?
How about me?
Is there still room for me in there?
You never left my heart, Jepoy.
[stutters] Really?
[giggles]
Really?
Maybe we should eat.
Sounds good.
[upbeat music playing]
Have a seat.
-[phone ringing]
-[laughing]
-Silly old cow.
-[phone ringing]
-Julio.
-Helena.
I'm touched. You have my number.
Why?
I even know your address.
Your number is nothing.
What about you? How did you get my number?
I have my ways.
Hmm. Stalker, much?
[laughs]
I can sense by the quiver in your voice…
that you're tickled
pink just talking to me.
[Julio laughs]
Oh, yeah.
I'm very excited about my lunch date.
Ooh. Someone I know?
Julio…
is that a tinge of jealousy that I hear?
Not really.
I also have someone coming over tonight.
Oh, really?
What are you serving?
I don't know yet.
But it's something…
bloody.
[chuckles]
Just how we like it.
Yes, just the way we like it.
[Helena laughs]
Be seeing you, Helena.
[laughs]
Damn, Helena,
I know you're still head
over heels in love with me.
I can read you like a book.
You…
you're so good-looking,
you're unbelievable.
[laughing]
Oh, this is going to be fun.
I'll get back at you, Diego Torillo.
[action music playing]
[Helena] Bring that inside.
Our guest is coming.
[sinister music playing]
[action music playing]
Lily!
Baby girl!
-Welcome to my home.
-Mama!
Mama, thanks for having me.
Of course!
I brought wine.
I did my research and found out
that this one's your favorite.
Excellent!
[eerie music]
Let's go in!
-Of course. Let's go.
-Come.
Oh. Excuse me.
For girls only.
Lily…
Lily, I've invited you to my home.
It seems like you don't trust me.
[chuckles]
Of course, I do, Mama.
Kindly wait outside.
-Happy?
-Of course!
How are we supposed to have girl talk
in the presence of your bodyguards?
[Lily chuckles]
Wow, Mama, your house is so big!
It's like a dragon's lair.
-It's huge.
-[Helena chuckles]
Lily, please come in.
Really, Mama, your house is so big.
Doesn't it scare you…
[Lily on TV screen]
…or make you feel lonely?
[Helena] No. Not at all. [chuckles]
You must be so hungry. Please sit down.
You may go.
Oh… [giggles]
I hope you like this!
Well, it looks delicious! So, let's eat?
Let's.
[suspenseful music playing]
Mmm…
Mm!
Wow, Mama.
-The fish tastes amazing.
-[Helena chuckles]
It's not fish.
Um…
If it's not fish, what is it?
It's snake.
[laughing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Nanny.
Diego… Are you on your way back?
Yes, Nanny. I'm headed home.
Nanny… Don't tell Uncle Pandoy this, okay?
But I bought him his favorite cake.
Just wait for me, okay?
[stutters] Okay. Just… Hurry home.
I'm almost there.
I'll be there in no time.
[tense music playing]
[Loring] All right.
[tense music continues playing]
You have to refrain
from calling me "Mama."
I'll call you by your first name.
Just call me Helena.
No, maybe I can call you, um…
Hel.
[Jose] We're all set, sir.
We're just waiting for Diego.
[Helena] They say you're indestructible.
I have nothing to hide from you now.
An eye for an eye, Red Dragon.
-What will you do to Diego?
-Diego.
-Stop resisting!
-[Diego screams]
Give me your gun!
-[Loring] Not Diego!
-[gunshot]
[distorted screams]
[theme music playing]